[
    {
        "front": "みすうみ",
        "back": "lake",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいきん",
        "back": "recently",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "ダイエット",
        "back": "diet",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "まわり",
        "back": "surroundings",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "きせつ",
        "back": "season",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "くうき",
        "back": "air",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことり",
        "back": "little bird",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "きこえる",
        "back": "to be heard",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "みえる",
        "back": "to be seen",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    },
    {
        "front": "きもちいい",
        "back": "to feel good",
        "chapter": "N4 C25"
    }
]